{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990012907","data":{"timestamp":" 947990012907"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990012966","data":{"timestamp":" 947990012966"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 646b0836-fc52-43f6-8736-6fae47090774"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_76"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990077360","data":{"timestamp":" 947990077360"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 95789adb-d81e-464c-baab-f17620dfacb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990087352","data":{"timestamp":" 947990087351"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 95789adb-d81e-464c-baab-f17620dfacb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990087440","data":{"timestamp":" 947990087440"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 95789adb-d81e-464c-baab-f17620dfacb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akajiunga nao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" WAKICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990097995","data":{"timestamp":" 947990097994"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 842ed502-a88b-4d24-a857-a0faf470ca1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990102403","data":{"timestamp":" 947990102403"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 842ed502-a88b-4d24-a857-a0faf470ca1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990104028","data":{"timestamp":" 947990104027"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 842ed502-a88b-4d24-a857-a0faf470ca1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990107259","data":{"timestamp":" 947990107259"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 842ed502-a88b-4d24-a857-a0faf470ca1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990108827","data":{"timestamp":" 947990108827"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 842ed502-a88b-4d24-a857-a0faf470ca1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990112278","data":{"timestamp":" 947990112278"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 842ed502-a88b-4d24-a857-a0faf470ca1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990113843","data":{"timestamp":" 947990113843"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 842ed502-a88b-4d24-a857-a0faf470ca1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990116480","data":{"timestamp":" 947990116480"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 842ed502-a88b-4d24-a857-a0faf470ca1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990118043","data":{"timestamp":" 947990118043"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 842ed502-a88b-4d24-a857-a0faf470ca1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990120243","data":{"timestamp":" 947990120243"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 842ed502-a88b-4d24-a857-a0faf470ca1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990121818","data":{"timestamp":" 947990121818"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 842ed502-a88b-4d24-a857-a0faf470ca1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990124641","data":{"timestamp":" 947990124641"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 842ed502-a88b-4d24-a857-a0faf470ca1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990126190","data":{"timestamp":" 947990126190"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 842ed502-a88b-4d24-a857-a0faf470ca1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990128932","data":{"timestamp":" 947990128932"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 842ed502-a88b-4d24-a857-a0faf470ca1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990130491","data":{"timestamp":" 947990130491"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 842ed502-a88b-4d24-a857-a0faf470ca1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990165435","data":{"timestamp":" 947990165435"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 842ed502-a88b-4d24-a857-a0faf470ca1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990165523","data":{"timestamp":" 947990165522"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 842ed502-a88b-4d24-a857-a0faf470ca1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990175503","data":{"timestamp":" 947990175503"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" acc4c92b-cf53-4d90-b840-2407b6c5070d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-2-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990181251","data":{"timestamp":" 947990181251"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" acc4c92b-cf53-4d90-b840-2407b6c5070d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-2-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990187128","data":{"timestamp":" 947990187128"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" acc4c92b-cf53-4d90-b840-2407b6c5070d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-2-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990187542","data":{"timestamp":" 947990187542"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" acc4c92b-cf53-4d90-b840-2407b6c5070d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-2-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990198653","data":{"timestamp":" 947990198653"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990203986","data":{"timestamp":" 947990203986"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990209766","data":{"timestamp":" 947990209765"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990217820","data":{"timestamp":" 947990217820"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990222825","data":{"timestamp":" 947990222825"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990228747","data":{"timestamp":" 947990228747"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990238534","data":{"timestamp":" 947990238533"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990245481","data":{"timestamp":" 947990245481"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990250366","data":{"timestamp":" 947990250366"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990258150","data":{"timestamp":" 947990258150"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990264409","data":{"timestamp":" 947990264409"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990269668","data":{"timestamp":" 947990269668"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990274954","data":{"timestamp":" 947990274954"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990280906","data":{"timestamp":" 947990280905"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990286565","data":{"timestamp":" 947990286565"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990294265","data":{"timestamp":" 947990294265"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990303156","data":{"timestamp":" 947990303156"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990307828","data":{"timestamp":" 947990307828"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990310655","data":{"timestamp":" 947990310655"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_76","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990318424","data":{"timestamp":" 947990318423"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" 8f5c6ca6-911b-4f18-a1f2-d35cdcdd9ef0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990348458","data":{"timestamp":" 947990348458"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" bd4e0a9e-5d89-4ebd-9645-482ef5d19fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990350513","data":{"timestamp":" 947990350513"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" bd4e0a9e-5d89-4ebd-9645-482ef5d19fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990351570","data":{"timestamp":" 947990351569"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" bd4e0a9e-5d89-4ebd-9645-482ef5d19fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990351638","data":{"timestamp":" 947990351638"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053303"," gameId":" bd4e0a9e-5d89-4ebd-9645-482ef5d19fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}